Guide to the Robert J. Levine Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Office Files, 1962-1997; Series II
  - Pfister, David, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 605)
  - Pickett, Larry, 1978-1981 (Box 18, Folder 606)
  - Piel, Jonathan, 1988-1992 (Box 18, Folder 607)
  - Pinto, Harlan, 1982-1991 (Box 18, Folder 608)
  - Piser, Phyllis, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 609)
  - Plattner, Stuart, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 610)
  - Plotnikoff, Greg, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 611)
  - Porter, George, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 612)
  - Porter, Joan, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 613)
  - Porter, Lane, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 614)
  - Pouncey, Claire, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 615)
  - Powledge, Tabitha, 1977-1989 (Box 18, Folder 616)
  - Prestegard, Elberta, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 617)
  - Price, Fred, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 618)
  - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 619)
  - Quintilliani, Richard, Undated (Box 18, Folder 620)
  - Quist, Norman, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 621)
  - Rabin, H. R., 1978-1983 (Box 18, Folder 622)
  - Rachlin, Joan, 1976-1986 (Box 18, Folder 623-624)
  - Rachmeler, Martin, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 625)
  - Raines, Lisa, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 626)
  - Rampe, Glenn, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 627)
  - Ramsey, Paul, 1973-1988 (Box 18, Folder 628)
  - Re, Richard, 1982-1983 (Box 18, Folder 629)
  - Reamer, Frederick, 1986-1991 (Box 18, Folder 630)
  - Reastig, Natalie, 1978-1987 (Box 18, Folder 631-632)
  - Redmond, Gene, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - Regan, Patricia, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - Regeneron, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 635-636)
  - Reidenberg, Marc, 1973-1987 (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - Reik, Hester, Undated (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - Reinstein, Jerome, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - Reiser, Morton, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - Relman, Arnold S., 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - Renault, Pierre, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - Reynolds, Herb, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - Richman, Susan, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - Rieselbach, Richard, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 645)
  - Riono, Pandu, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 646)
  - Riskin, Leonard L., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 647)
  - Roberts, David, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 648)
  - Robinson, Donald, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - Rodriguez, William, YMS-1, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 650)
  - Rodwin, Marc, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 651)
  - Roffman, Roger, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - Rogers, Audrey, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 653)
  - Rohrl, Michael, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 654)
  - Rolen, J. Frazer, Jr., 1991 (Box 19, Folder 655)
  - Rome, Howard P., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 656)
  - Romero, Roberto, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 657)
  - Rosen, Saul, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 658)
  - Roth, Daniel, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 659)
  - Roy, David, 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 660)
  - Rubio, Cindy, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 661)
  - St. John, Ron, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 662)
  - Sanzari, Neil, 1974-1981 (Box 19, Folder 663)
  - Sapirstein, Wolf, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 664)
  - Sartorelli, Alan C., 1978-1985 (Box 19, Folder 665)
  - Sato, Tatsuo, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 666)
  - Sawyer, Forrest, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 667)
  - Scarf, Maggie, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 668)
  - Scarr, Sandra, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 669)
  - Scher, Stephen, 1982-1993 (Box 19, Folder 670)
  - Schipper, Harvey, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 671)
  - Schwartz, Robert, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 672)
  - Sears, Marvin L., 1981 (Box 19, Folder 673)
  - Sedransk, Nell, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 674)
  - Segota, Ivan, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 675)
  - Seldin, Donald, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 676)
  - Selleck, Nathaniel, 1973-1996 (Box 19, Folder 677)
  - Senay, Edward, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 678)
  - Shambaugh, Vicki, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 679)
  - Shamoo, Adil, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 680-681)
  - Shanks, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 682)
  - Shannon, Thomas A., 1983 (Box 19, Folder 683-684)
  - Shapiro, David, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 685)
  - Shaw, Daniel, 1973-1996 (Box 19, Folder 686)
  - Shaw, Margery, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 687)
  - Sheard, Michael, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 688)
  - Sheldon, Richard C., 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 689)
  - Shenk, Ian, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 690)
  - Sheridan, Edythe, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 691)
  - Sherwin, Robert, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 692)
  - Shetler, Judy C., 1973-1996 (Box 19, Folder 693)
  - Shewmon, D. Alan, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 694)
  - Shubin, Seymour, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 695)
  - Siegal, Alan, 1994-1995 (Box 19, Folder 696)
  - Silbert, Jerry, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 697)
  - Silbert, Roberta, 1978-1990 (Box 19, Folder 698)
  - Simon, Greg, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 699)
  - Simpson, Gary, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 700)
  - Sims, Stephen, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 701)
  - Singer, Merianne, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 702)
  - Sister Mary Louise, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 703)
  - Slack, Charles, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 704)
  - Smith, C. Thomas, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 706)
  - Smith, David, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 719)
  - Smith, Martin, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 705)
  - Society for Bioethics Consultation
    - 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 707-708)
    - 1987-1993 (Box 20, Folder 709)
    - Abstracts, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 710)
    - Board, 1993 May (Box 20, Folder 711)
  - Soffer, Alfred, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 711A)
  - Solberg, Mary, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 712-715)
  - Solen, Gwen, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 716)
  - Solnit, Albert, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 717)
  - Sorenson, John, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 718)
  - Spicker, Stuart, 1976-1979 (Box 20, Folder 720)
  - Spilker, Bert, 1987-1992 (Box 20, Folder 721-722)
  - Spinelli, Nick, 1985, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 723)
  - Spital, Aaron, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 724)
  - Spodick, David, 1982-1986 (Box 20, Folder 725)
  - Spriggs, Dale, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 726)
  - Stanley, Barbara, 1980-1993 (Box 20, Folder 727)
  - Starkman, Bernard, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 728)
  - Steinfels, Peter, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 729)
  - Stellar, Eliot, 1975-1987 (Box 20, Folder 730)
  - Stern, Janice, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 731)
  - Stern, Jessie, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 732)
  - Stern, Robert, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 733)
  - Sternberg, David, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 734)
  - Stidham, Gerg, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 735)
  - Stoch, Aubrey, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 736)
  - Stockwell, Serena, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 737)
  - Straus, Stephen, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 738)
  - Strauss, Jerome, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 739)
  - Streeter, Debby, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 740)
  - Stubing, William, 1990-1994 (Box 20, Folder 741-742)
  - Stunkard, Albert, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 743)
  - Taub, Sheila, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 744)
  - Taylor, Catherine, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 745)
  - Taylor, James S., 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 746)
  - Taylor, W. J. Russell, 1985-1988 (Box 20, Folder 747)
  - Terrill-Brever, Judith, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 748)
  - Thaler, Naomi, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 749)
  - Thaler, Paul, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 750)
  - Thomas, John, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 751)
  - Thomas, Lewis, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 752)
  - Thomas, Selma, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 753)
  - Thompson, Ernest, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 754)
  - Thornton, George F., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 755)
  - Tibbles, Lance, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 756)
  - Tiefel, Hans, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 757)
  - Tilson, David, 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 758)
  - Time Magazine, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 759)
  - Titus, Linda, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 760)
  - Todd, Mary, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 761)
  - Tripp, Edward, 1982-1987 (Box 20, Folder 762)
  - True, A. Curtis, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 763)
  - Tucker, W. Randolph, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 764)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1983-1985 (Box 20, Folder 765)
  - Tyson, Jon E., 1988 (Box 20, Folder 766)
  - Uffelmann, Hans, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 767)
  - Underwood, Arthur, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 768)
  - Van Citters, Robert, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 769)
  - VandeCreek, Larry, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 770)
  - van Eys, Jan, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 771)
  - Vargus, Jilda, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 772)
  - Vaux, Kenneth, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 773)
  - Vella, Charles, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 774)
  - Villar, Jesus, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 775)
  - Vincineau, Michel, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 776)
  - Viscarello, Rich, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 777)
  - Viseltear, Arthur, 1968-1989 (Box 21, Folder 778)
  - Vlock, Laurel, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 779)
  - Vodra, William, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 780)
  - Waife, S. O., 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 781)
  - Wald, Florence, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 782)
  - Walters, James, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 783)
  - Waniek, Marilyn, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 784)
  - Wannarka, Gerald, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 785)
  - Wara, Diane, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 786)
  - Wardell, William, 1975-1992 (Box 21, Folder 787)
  - Warner, Joseph S., 1973-1983 (Box 21, Folder 788-789)
  - Watkins, Judith, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 790)
  - Watson, John, 1983-1991 (Box 21, Folder 791)
  - Weiner, Alan, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 792)
  - Weinstein, Bruce, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 793)
  - Weinstein, Deena, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 794)
  - Weissman, Myrna, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 795)
  - Weisstub, David, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 796)
  - Wenger, Nanette, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 797)
  - Westerman, Jacqueline, 1974-1997 (Box 21, Folder 798-799)
  - Wexler, Nancy, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 800)
  - Whitehorne, Hurlstone, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 801)
  - Wilkenson, Jane, Undated (Box 21, Folder 802)
  - Williams, Anna Lisle, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 803)
  - Williams, Erin, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 804)
  - Williams, O. Dale, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 805)
  - Williams-Ashman, Anne, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 806)
  - Willis, David, 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 807)
  - Willman, Vallee, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 808)
  - Willner, Henry, 1974-1987 (Box 21, Folder 809)
  - Wilson, Courtland, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 810)
  - Wilson, Linda S., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 811)
  - Wilson, Vivian D., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 812)
  - Wilt, Timothy, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 813)
  - Winikoff, Beverly, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 814)
  - Winship, Daniel, 1971-1980 (Box 21, Folder 815)
  - Winslade, William J., 1979-1993 (Box 21, Folder 816)
  - Winsten, Jay, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 817)
  - Winter, David, 1987-1992 (Box 21, Folder 818)
  - Winter, Phillip, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 819)
  - Winter, Thorne S., 1971 (Box 21, Folder 820)
  - Wirt, Roger, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 821)
  - Wittman, Meg, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 822)
  - Wohlgelernter, Daniel, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 823)
  - Wolff, Laura, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 824)
  - Wolinsky, Howard, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 825)
  - Wood, John, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 826)
  - Woodruff, William, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 827)
  - Woodward, William, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 828)
  - World Health Organization, 1988-1990 (Box 21, Folder 829-830)
  - Worrall, Paul, 1980-1987 (Box 21, Folder 831)
  - Wright, Clinton, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 832)
  - Wright, David, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 833)
  - Wroblewski, Rita, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 834)
  - Wurtman, Richard, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 835)
  - Yancik, Rosemary, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 836)
  - Yeary, Marie, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 837)
  - Yepner, Raymond, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 838)
  - Yesley, Michael, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 839)
  - Yimoyines, Constantine, Undated (Box 22, Folder 840)
  - Zadunaisky, J. A., 1993 (Box 22, Folder 841)
  - Zallen, Doris T., 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 842)
  - Zappacosta, Robert, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 843)
  - Zarafonetis, Chris J. D., 1969-1981 (Box 22, Folder 844)
  - Zelis, Robert, 1973-1977 (Box 22, Folder 845)
  - Zito, Ruben, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 846)
  - Zox, Alan, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 847)
  - Zuger, Abigail, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 848)
- Medical ethics course materials, 1978-1996; Series III
  This series comprises readings, course notes, and student work relating to medical ethics courses taught by Levine at the Yale School of Medicine.
  Materials are arranged by material type and chronologically therein.
  - Materials on Professional Responsibility, by Katz, Jay and Robert J. Levine, 1989 January (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Materials on Professional Responsibility, by Levine, Robert J., Angela R. Holder and Bruce Baker
    - Volume II, 1990 March (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Volume I, 1991 January (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Volume II, 1991 March (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Course reading packet, 1996 spring (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Scenarios, Circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Class handouts, Circa 1980s (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Farley, Margaret, 1996 spring (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Materials for classes: class lists, lecture notes, miscellaneous
    - 1985 fall (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - 1984 fall (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - 1982 fall-1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - 1982 spring (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - 1981 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 1978 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Contents of binder for class of 1982: class lists, syllabi, lecture notes, readings (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Contents of binder for class of 1986: class lists, syllabi, lecture notes, readings (Box 23, Folder 17-19)
  - Plans for class meetings, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Editorial files for IRB: A Journal of Human Subjects Research, 1976-1996; Series IV
  This series comprises correspondence, drafts, rejections, and other materials relating to Levine's many years editing the projessional journal IRB (Institutional Review Board).
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by personal last name, organization name, or topic.
  - Abram, Morris, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Abramovich, Rona, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Abramson, Paul R., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - AIDS, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Alazraki, Naomi, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Altman, Jacki, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Amiel, Stephanie, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, James R., 1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Angoff, Nancy, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Arbet, Harvey, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Arnstein, Robert, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Auer, Matthew, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Balaban, Donald, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Bannon, James A., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Barclay, Gordon, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Baron, Robert A., 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Barry, Michele, 1981-1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Behrens, Diane R., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Benbassat, Jochanan, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Bergkamp, Lucas, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Berkman, Lisa, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Best, William R., 1985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Betak, John F., 1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Bjune, Gunnar, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Blake, David, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Bonkovsky, Frederick, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Boruch, Robert, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Bowker, W. F., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Brown, Philip M., 1994 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Brown, Stuart, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Buckingham, Robert, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Burtchaell, James, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Busch, David, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Cancer drugs, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Cann, Cristina, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Cantor, Dianne, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Carson, Ronald A., 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Cashore, William, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Chlebowski, Rowan, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Christakis, Nicholas, 1985-1994 (Box 24, Folder 40-42)
  - Cleary, Robert E., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Cohen, Jeffrey M. and William B. Hedberg, 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Compensation, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Connelly, R. J., 1985-1987 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Connor, William H., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Coombs, Robert, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Costa, Paul, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Cowan, Dale, 1979-1989 (Box 25, Folder 50-51)
  - Crawford-Brown, Douglas J., 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Cupples, Brian, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Dae-Re, R., 1991-1995 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Daniels, Richard, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Darvall, Leanna, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Davis, Dena, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - DeChristoforo, Robert, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Des Jarlais, Don, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Diers, Donna, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Dingfelder, William, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Donabella, Maria, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 61A)
  - Donehew, Gerald, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Dubler, Nancy, 1982-1991 (Box 25, Folder 63-65)
  - Dustan, Harriet, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Dyer, Allen, 1981-1987 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Eichwald, E. J., 1981 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Epstein, William, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Fine, Alan, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Finkel, Marion, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Flournoy, Nancy, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Fost-Robertson Case Study, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Freeberg, Fred E., 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Freedman, Larry, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Freeman, William, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 76-78)
  - Gallant, Dean, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Gamble, Harold F., 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Garb, Solomon, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Garfinkel, Simson, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Geller, Jeffrey, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Gergen, Ken, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Gillcrist, Bernadette, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Goldberg, Harold, 1985-1992 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Goldberg, Jacquelyn, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Goldhammer, Muriel, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Goldman, Jerry and Martin D. Katz, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Goldstein, Richard, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Gordon, Bruce, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Gordon, Robert, 1977-1984 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Grayzel, Arthur, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Greene, Penelope J., 1982-1986 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - Grinnell, Fred, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - Haldeman, Nancy, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Hall, Andy, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Hall, David, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - Hallstrom, Al, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Harris, W. Edward, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Harrison, Christine, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Heath, Erica, 1979-1993 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - Heinze-Lacey, Beverly, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 103)
  - Helgartner, Stephen, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 107)
  - Heller, Marc, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 108)
  - Herceg-Baron, Roberta, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 104)
  - Herman, Samuel, 1977-1988 (Box 26, Folder 105)
  - Hershey, Nathan, 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 106)
  - Hodge, Milton, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 109)
  - Holder, Angela R., 1978-1993 (Box 26, Folder 110-111)
  - Holm, Soren, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 112)
  - Houston, Mark A., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 113)
  - Howard, Jan, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 114)
  - Ickovics, Jeannette, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 115)
  - Inquiry, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 116)
  - IRB
    - 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 117-118)
    - Culpepper project, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 119)
    - Ideas, notes, 1979-1990 (Box 26, Folder 120)
    - Index, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 121)
    - Mailing lists, 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 122)
  - Jackson, C. E., 1980 (Box 26, Folder 123)
  - Jellinek, Michael S., 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 124)
  - Johnson, Arthur, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 125)
  - Juengst, Eric, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 126)
  - Jumel, Mignon, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 127)
  - Kass, Nancy, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 128)
  - Kassler, William J., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 129)
  - Katz, Jay, 1980-1986 (Box 26, Folder 130)
  - Kaushik, Vijay, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 131)
  - Kelsey, Jennifer, 1980-1984 (Box 26, Folder 132)
  - Kennedy, B. J., 1979 (Box 26, Folder 133)
  - Koff, Wayne, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 134)
  - Koren, Gideon, 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 135)
  - Kowal, J. P., 1979 (Box 26, Folder 136)
  - Krushak, William, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 137)
  - Kurt, Thomas, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 138)
  - Lackey, Douglas P., 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 139)
  - Lamont-Havers, Ron, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 140)
  - La Puma, John, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 141)
  - Lathrop, Vallory, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 142)
  - Lawson, Sara, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 143)
  - Leblang, Theodore, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 144)
  - Leikin, Sanford, 1982-1993 (Box 27, Folder 145)
  - Leonard, Colin, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 146)
  - Levine, Carol, 1988-1993 (Box 27, Folder 147-148)
  - Levine, Robert J.
    - 1981 November, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 149)
    - Case Study
      - 1984 June (Box 27, Folder 150)
      - 1979 (Box 27, Folder 151)
      - Consent to nondisclosure, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 152)
    - Cash payments, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 153)
    - Changing regulations #2, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 154)
    - Children's regulations, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 155)
    - Editorial #1, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 156)
    - Market, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 157)
    - On Hogue, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 158)
    - Placebo, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 159)
    - S.1075, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 160)
    - Treating the troops, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 161)
    - Food and Drug Administration (FDA): Treatment investigational new drugs (INDs), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 162)
  - Levine, Murray, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 163)
  - Lewis, Jerry P., 1988 (Box 27, Folder 164)
  - Lewis, Jessica, 1979-1984 (Box 27, Folder 165)
  - Lewis, Melvin, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - Liddle, Becky, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Lind, Stuart, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Louttit, Richard, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 169)
  - Lustig, B. Andrew, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 170)
  - MacKay, Charles, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - Mahler, Mark, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Maienza, Jeffrey, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 173)
  - Makuch, Robert, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 174)
  - Marcus, Steven, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 175)
  - Margolies, Michael, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 176)
  - Marks, Eric, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 177)
  - Marquis, Don, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 178)
  - Marshall, Ernest, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 179)
  - Martin, Douglas K., 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 180)
  - Masse, F. X., 1985 (Box 27, Folder 181)
  - Mathews, Christopher, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 182)
  - McCrae, Robert, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 183)
  - McGough, Helen, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 184)
  - McGrath, Katherine, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 185)
  - McLarty, Jerry, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 188)
  - McMahon, F. Gilbert, 1982-1987 (Box 27, Folder 186)
  - McNeill, Paul M., 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 187)
  - Medical Ethics course, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 189-190)
  - Meisel, Alan, 1981-1990 (Box 28, Folder 191)
  - Meyer, Lynn, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 192)
  - Meyers, Karin, 1976-1989 (Box 28, Folder 193)
  - Michaels, Erica, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 194)
  - Miller, Bruce L., 1979-1991 (Box 28, Folder 195-196)
  - Miller, Emily, 1980-1986 (Box 28, Folder 197)
  - Miller, Judith, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 198)
  - Miranda, Gary, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 199)
  - Mishkin, Barbara, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 200)
  - Mitchell, Sheila, 1987-1988 (Box 28, Folder 201)
  - Mizruchi, Ephraim, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 202)
  - Mueller, Maurice, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 203)
  - Mulder, Jannes H., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 204)
  - Murphy, William D., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 205)
  - Nitschke, Ruprecht, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 206)
  - Nolan, Kathleen, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 207)
  - Nottingham, Stu, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 208)
  - Nyborg, Wesley, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 209)
  - Ockene, Ira, 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 210)
  - O'Neil, Terence, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 211)
  - Orr, Robert D., 1995 (Box 28, Folder 212)
  - Osborne, L. W., 1982 (Box 28, Folder 213)
  - Ostfeld, Adrian, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 214)
  - O'Sullivan, Gwen, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 215)
  - Papa, Chris, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 216)
  - Parker, Lisa, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 217)
  - Pattullo, E. L., 1979-1991 (Box 28, Folder 218-219)
  - Perry, Clifton, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 221)
  - Perry, Samuel, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 222)
  - Peterson, Barry, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - Phalen, Robert F. and Beth H. Wagner, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 225)
  - Phillips, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 223)
  - Phillips, Sarah, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 224)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 226)
  - Prentice, Ernest D., 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 227)
  - Prieto, Jorge, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 228)
  - Primovic, Jeffrey, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 229)
  - Provost, Denise, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 230)